KAMYAB ROUHIFAR

19 Copperstone Cres. Richmond Hill, ON L4S 2C5 Phone: 437-984-5385

E-mail: <u>karouhifar@gmail.com</u>
Website: <u>https://www.kamyabrouhifar.ca</u>

SUMMARY

The high-performing individual with a proven ability to establish compatibility with clients. Highly enthusiastic and dependable customer service professional with more than one year of client interface experience. Dedicated Customer Service associate motivated to maintain customer relationships and company success.

EDUCATION

Computer Programming and Analysis

Sept 2019 – Present

Seneca College, Toronto

Award:

President's Honor List Winter 2021, President's Honor List Fall 2020, Bachelor of Tech Software Development Scholarship Fall 2019.

- Programmed web development projects using Node.js, React.JS, JavaScript (jQuery), CSS (Bootstrap).
- Installation and setup of Oracle SQL Community servers using C/C++, Java application on Windows/Linux.
- Utilized web applications connected to MongoDB server Database.
- designed data structures, algorithms, and object-oriented programming in the exact specification

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming C/C++, Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript (jQuery)
Database MS SQL, MySQL, Oracle SQL, MongoDB

Frameworks / Tools Bootstrap, jQuery, Node JS, Express JS, React JS, Angular, React Native IDE Tools MS Office, Eclipse, IntelliJ IDEA, MS Visual Studio, MS Visual Studio Code

Version Control Git, GitHub, Azure DevOps Server

Case Modeling Visual Paradigm, Draw.io

Cloud Platform AWS Elastic Beanstalk, Heroku, Netlify, Google Firebase

Operating System Windows, Linux/Unix

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

Server-Side Web applications using Node.js and Express

GitHub: https://github.com/krouhifar/WebServerProject Heroku: https://fast-castle-87951.herokuapp.com/

- Created web pages for administrator, user, and visitor's interface.
- Used HTML 5, CSS3, Vanilla JavaScript, Node.JS, Express and the Handlebars templating engine.
- User data access by MongoDB Database, Google-OAuth 2.0 APIs server.

Web REST API using ReactJS

GitHub: https://github.com/krouhifar/ReactRestaurantAPI

Netlify: https://kamyabreactrestaurant.netlify.app

- Open-source JavaScript frameworks and libraries (React, jQuery, Bootstraps, GSAP, and Leaflet).
- The concept (and application) of front-end web client development.
- A survey of widely-used current front-end development environments.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack App Developer (Co-op)

Ideal Ventures, Markham

Jun 2021 – Sept 2021

- Researched and built a POC mobile app development by using React Native mobile application.
- Manage application requirement and project coordination through Azure DevOps tools.
- Maintained and administered GIT source code repository through Azure DevOps tools.
- Experienced in working with Angular 10 modules, services, directives, and dependency injection.
- Responsible for creating RESTFUL Web Services to serve data to the front-end application in JSON format.
- Created a custom responsive web application to robust a line-of-business web application using Angular.

Backroom Fulfillment Associate

Sept 2020 - Aug 2021

Walmart, Richmond Hill

- Responsible for the processing of orders and shipments according to company policies and procedures.
- Followed company package/shipping standards ensuring all customers received all online order pickups in excellent condition.
- Determined customer needs by asking relevant questions and listening actively to their response.
- Read and comprehend job orders.
- Trained in picking, sorting, packing, and binning.

Activity and Memberships

- Basketball Player.
- CPR and AED First Aid certified.
- Electric Pallet Jack certified.